{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "VGhlIFNlY29uZCBCb2VyIFdhciBpbiAxODk5IHdhcyBmb3VnaHQgd2hlcmU/",
            "correct_answer": "U291dGggQWZyaWNh",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "QXJnZW50aW5h",
                "TmVwYWw=",
                "QnVsZ2FyaWE="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaXMgdGhlIGh1bGwgTk8uIG9mIHRoZSBGbGV0Y2hlciBjbGFzcyBkZXN0cm95ZXIgRmxldGNoZXI/",
            "correct_answer": "REQtNDQ1",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "REQtOTky",
                "REQtNDQ0",
                "REQtNDQ2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgZm91bmQgaW4gMTk0NiBieSB0d28geW91bmcgc2hlcGFyZHMgbmVhciBhIGNhdmU/",
            "correct_answer": "RGVhZCBTZWEgU2Nyb2xscw==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "VGhlIEJsYWNrYmVhcmQgQ2hlc3Q=",
                "U2hlZXA=",
                "VGhlIEZpcnN0IE9heGFjYSBDYXZlIFNsZWVwZXI="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIEdlcm1hbiBvZmZlbnNpdmUgb3BlcmF0aW9uIGluIE9jdG9iZXIgMTk0MSB0byB0YWtlIE1vc2NvdyBiZWZvcmUgd2ludGVyPw==",
            "correct_answer": "T3BlcmF0aW9uIFR5cGhvb24=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "T3BlcmF0aW9uIFN1bmZsb3dlcg==",
                "T3BlcmF0aW9uIEJhcmJhcm9zc2E=",
                "Q2FzZSBCbHVl"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hvIGludmVudGVkIHRoZSAiRmx5aW5nIFNodXR0bGUiIGluIDE3Mzg7IG9uZSBvZiB0aGUga2V5IGRldmVsb3BtZW50cyBpbiB0aGUgaW5kdXN0cmlhbGl6YXRpb24gb2Ygd2VhdmluZz8=",
            "correct_answer": "Sm9obiBLYXk=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "SmFtZXMgSGFyZ3JlYXZlcw==",
                "UmljaGFyZCBBcmt3cmlnaHQ=",
                "Sm9obiBEZWVyZQ=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "VG91c3NhaW50IExvdXZlcnR1cmUgbGVkIGEgc3VjY2Vzc2Z1bCBzbGF2ZSByZXZvbHQgaW4gd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeT8=",
            "correct_answer": "SGFpdGk=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "RnJhbmNl",
                "Q3ViYQ==",
                "VW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcw=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "VGhlIGNvYXQgb2YgYXJtcyBvZiB0aGUgS2luZyBvZiBTcGFpbiBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgYXJtcyBmcm9tIHRoZSBtb25hcmNocyBvZiBDYXN0aWxsZSwgTGVvbiwgQXJhZ29uIGFuZCB3aGljaCBvdGhlciBmb3JtZXIgSWJlcmlhbiBraW5nZG9tPw==",
            "correct_answer": "TmF2YXJyZQ==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "R2FsaWNpYQ==",
                "R3JhbmFkYQ==",
                "Q2F0YWxvbmlh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "T24gd2hpY2ggZGF5IGRpZCBBUlBBTkVUIHN1ZmZlciBhIDQgaG91ciBsb25nIG5ldHdvcmsgY3Jhc2g/",
            "correct_answer": "T2N0b2JlciAyNywgMTk4MA==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Tm92ZW1iZXIgMjEsIDE5Njk=",
                "T2N0b2JlciAyOSwgMTk2OQ==",
                "RGVjZW1iZXIgOSwgMTk5MQ=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHJlYWwgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgQWxiYW5pYW4gbmF0aW9uYWwgbGVhZGVyIFNrYW5kZXJiZWc/",
            "correct_answer": "R2plcmdqIEthc3RyaW90aQ==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "RGl0dXJhayBaaHVsYXRp",
                "SXNrYW5kZXIgQmVqa28=",
                "TWlyYXNoIEtyYXNuaWtp"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgd29tZW4gam9pbmVkIHRoZSBVbml0ZWQgU3RhdGVzIEFybWVkIFNlcnZpY2VzIGR1cmluZyBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSUk/",
            "correct_answer": "MzUwLDAwMA==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "MjI1LDAwMA==",
                "MTAwLDAwMA==",
                "NTAwLDAwMA=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggZGF5IGRpZCBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSSBiZWdpbj8=",
            "correct_answer": "SnVseSAyOA==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "SmFudWFyeSAyOA==",
                "SnVuZSAyOA==",
                "QXByaWwgMjg="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "QWZ0ZXIgdGhlIDE1MTYgQmF0dGxlIG9mIE1hcmogRGFiaXEsIHRoZSBPdHRvbWFuIEVtcGlyZSB0b29rIGNvbnRyb2wgb2YgSmVydXNhbGVtIGZyb20gd2hpY2ggc3VsdGFuYXRlPw==",
            "correct_answer": "TWFtbHVr",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "QXl5dWJpZA==",
                "VW1tYXl5YWQ=",
                "U2VsanVx"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "VGhlIG9udG9sb2dpY2FsIGFyZ3VtZW50IGZvciB0aGUgcHJvb2Ygb2YgR29kJ3MgZXhpc3RlbmNlIGlzIGZpcnN0IGF0dHJpYnV0ZWQgdG8gd2hvbT8=",
            "correct_answer": "QW5zZWxtIG9mIENhbnRlcmJ1cnk=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "UmVuw6kgRGVzY2FydGVz",
                "SW1tYW51ZWwgS2FudA==",
                "QXJpc3RvdGxl"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgdGhlb3JldGljYWwgcGh5Y2lzaXN0cyBmaXJzdCBwcmVkaWN0ZWQgdGhlIGV4aXN0ZW5jZSBvZiBhbnRpbWF0dGVyPw==",
            "correct_answer": "UGF1bCBEaXJhYw==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "TmllbHMgQm9ocg==",
                "QWxiZXJ0IEVpbnN0ZWlu",
                "V2VybmVyIEhlaXNlbmJlcmc="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgQm9laW5nIEItMjkgdGhhdCBkcm9wcGVkIHRoZSAnTGl0dGxlIEJveScgYXRvbWljIGJvbWIgb24gSGlyb3NoaW1hPw==",
            "correct_answer": "RW5vbGEgR2F5",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "TmVjZXNzYXJ5IEV2aWw=",
                "VGhlIEdyZWF0IEFydGlzdGU=",
                "RnVsbCBIb3VzZQ=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "VGhlIG1haW4gb2JqZWN0aXZlIG9mIHRoZSBHZXJtYW4gb3BlcmF0aW9uICJDYXNlIEJsdWUiIGR1cmluZyBXb3JsZCBXYXIgSUkgd2FzIG9yaWdpbmFsbHkgdG8gY2FwdHVyZSB3aGF0Pw==",
            "correct_answer": "Q2F1Y2FzdXM=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "U3RhbGluZ3JhZA==",
                "Q3JpbWVh",
                "Vm9yb25lemg="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcG9zaXRpb25zIGRpZCB0aGUgYXN0cm9ub21lciBhbmQgcGh5c2ljaXN0IElzYWFjIE5ld3RvbiBub3QgaG9sZD8=",
            "correct_answer": "U3VydmV5b3IgdG8gdGhlIENpdHkgb2YgTG9uZG9u",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "UHJvZmVzc29yIG9mIE1hdGhlbWF0aWNz",
                "V2FyZGVuIG9mIHRoZSBSb3lhbCBNaW50",
                "TWVtYmVyIG9mIFBhcmxpYW1lbnQ="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb25lIG9mIHRoZXNlIHJ1bGVycyBkaWQgbm90IGJlbG9uZyB0byB0aGUgSGFic2J1cmcgZHluYXN0eT8=",
            "correct_answer": "UGhpbGlwIFY=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Q2hhcmxlcyBW",
                "UGhpbGlwIElJ",
                "RnJhbmNpcyBKb3NlcGg="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "VGhlIHBhbnRoZW9uIGluIFJvbWUgd2FzIHVzZWQgdG8gd29yc2hpcCB3aGF0IGdvZD8=",
            "correct_answer": "QW55IGdvZCB0aGV5IHdhbnRlZA==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "QXRoZW5h",
                "WmV1cw==",
                "Qm90aCBBdGhlbmEgYW5kIFpldXM="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "aGFyZA==",
            "category": "SGlzdG9yeQ==",
            "question": "V2hvIGFzc2Fzc2luYXRlZCBQcmVzaWRlbnQgSmFtZXMgQS4gR2FyZmllbGQ/",
            "correct_answer": "Q2hhcmxlcyBHdWl0ZWF1",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "U2lyaGFuIFNpcmhhbg==",
                "TGVvbiBDem9sZ29zeg==",
                "Sm9obiBXaWxrZXMgQm9vdGg="
            ]
        }
    ]
}